{
    "subject": "resource/WESM",
    "predicate": "ontology/programmeFormat",
    "object": "resource/All-news_radio",
    "human_readable": "The programme format of WESM is all-news radio.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7089473605155945,
            "question": "What type of radio programming does WESM use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6230562925338745,
            "question": "Is WESM a talk radio station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6019899249076843,
            "question": "What is the main focus of programming on WESM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5718522667884827,
            "question": "Is WESM a commercial radio station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4819009602069855,
            "question": "Are there any specific themes or topics covered by WESM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48096364736557007,
            "question": "How would you describe the tone of programming on WESM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4513540267944336,
            "question": "What kind of content is featured on WESM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37995174527168274,
            "question": "What is the target audience for WESM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2938304543495178,
            "question": "Would you expect to hear sports updates on WESM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2840082049369812,
            "question": "Does WESM play music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The programme format of WESM is all-news radio.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3296_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you expect to hear sports updates on WESM?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3296_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the target audience for WESM?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3296_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of content is featured on WESM?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3296_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3296_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3296_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3296_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3296_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3296_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3296_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3296_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3296_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3296_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3296_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because none of the documents mention that the program format of WESM is all-news radio. In fact, they describe it as broadcasting a variety of formats, including jazz, news and information, blues, world, American folk music, and gospel programming (see file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3296/re-ranker-msmarco/27.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided do not support the statement that \"The programme format of WESM is all-news radio.\" Instead, the documents indicate that WESM broadcasts a variety of formats including jazz, news and information, blues, world, American folk music, and gospel programming."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}